Guide to the Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét papers
1829-1962
1920-1943
YCAL MSS 1046
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
87.54
143 boxes + 3 broadsides
Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1898-1943
Benét, Rosemary, 1900-1962
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Acquired primarily through gift from Stephen Vincent Benét, Rosemary Benét, and the estate of Rosemary Benét, 1942-1966.
Conditions Governing Access
The materials are open for research.
Boxes 138-143: Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
Stephen Vincent Benét (1898-1943) and Rosemary Benét (1900-1962)
Stephen Vincent Benét was a well known and widely read author in the United States during the 1930s and 1940s. After the success of his long poem, John Brown's Body (1928), for which he was awarded a Pulitzer Prize in 1929, he regularly published poems, short stories, and other work in popular magazines such as The Atlantic Monthly, The New Yorker, and The Saturday Evening Post. His short story, "The Devil and Daniel Webster" (1936) was awarded the O. Henry Memorial Award in 1937. In addition to poetry and short stories, he is the author of novels, book reviews, essays, radio and stage plays, screenplays, and speeches.
Rosemary Benét, born Rosemary Carr, is the author of poems, book reviews, essays, and short stories. She and her husband co-authored A Book of Americans (1933), a book of poems for children about prominent figures in American history.
Bibliographic, biographical, and critical studies on Stephen Vincent and Rosemary Benét include books by Mary Dearing Lewis (1952), Charles A. Fenton (1958), David Garret Izzo and Lincoln Konkle (2003), and Evelyn Helmick Hively (2011). Summary information is also available in the standard print and online biographical resources.
Scope and Contents
The Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét papers consist of correspondence, manuscripts, printed material, and personal and family papers documenting the life and work of American authors Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary Benét. The collection spans the years 1829 to 1962, with the bulk of the collection dating from roughly 1910 to 1943.
Collection material is chiefly in English; with some material in French, German, Polish, and Swedish.
Arrangement
Organized into six series: I. Correspondence, 1887-1962. II. Family Correspondence, 1829-1962. III. Writings, 1870-1962. IV. Printed Appearances of Writings by Stephen Vincent Benét, 1916-1958. V. Printed Material, 1836-1962. VI. Personal Papers, 1843-1962.
Related Materials
Material by or relating to Stephen Vincent and Rosemary Benét acquired by the library from other Benét family sources can be located in the Benét Family Papers (YCAL MSS 1107). Material by or relating to Stephen Vincent Benét acquired by the library from non-family sources is located in the Benét Family Collection (YCAL MSS 1108). Additional material by or relating to Stephen Vincent and Rosemary Benét can also be found in the William Rose Benét Papers (YCAL MSS 1100).
American literature -- 20th Century; Authors, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Poets, American -- 20th Century -- Archives; Europe -- Social life and customs -- 20th Century; Photographic prints; Authors -- United States -- 20th Century; Poets -- United States -- 20th Century; Abbe, George, 1911-1989; Barry, Philip, 1896-1949; Benét, Rosemary, 1900-1962; Benét, Stephen Vincent, 1898-1943; Bingham, Hiram, 1875-1956; Carter, John Franklin, 1897-1967; Cousins, Norman, 1912-1990; Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1862-1948; Dos Passos, John, 1896-1970; Engle, Paul, 1908-1991; Fenton, Charles A., 1919-1960; Ficke, Arthur Davison, 1883-1945; Fletcher, John Gould, 1886-1950; Lewis, Sinclair, 1885-1951; MacLeish, Archibald, 1892-1982; McClure, Robert E.; Moore, Douglas, 1893-1969; Myers, Richard, 1901-1977; Nathan, Robert, 1894-1985; Patchen, Kenneth, 1911-1972; Potter, Beatrix, 1866-1943; Rukeyser, Muriel, 1913-1980; Sandburg, Carl, 1878-1967; Semple, Ellen Churchill, 1863-1932; Wilder, Thornton, 1897-1975; Brandt & Brandt; Council for Democracy; Doubleday, Doran & Company; Farrar & Rinehart; Yale University. Alumni
- Correspondence, 1887-1962; Series I; 16.18; 35 boxes
  Arrangement
  Organized into two subseries: General Correspondence and Third Party Correspondence. General Correspondence is arranged alphabetically by correspondent and chronologically within files. Third Party Correspondence is arranged alphabetically.
  Scope and Contents
  Series I. General Correspondence consists chiefly of single letters and small groups of incoming personal and professional correspondence to Stephen Vincent Benét and Rosemary (Carr) Benét. There are letters from many English-language authors and literary critics of the first half of the twentieth century, as well as from friends, publishers, editors of journals and newspapers, literary, cultural, and civic organizations, academic institutions, and federal agencies. Larger files can be found for authors George Abbe, Paul Engle, and Robert Nathan, for Stephen Vincent Benét's biographer, Charles A. Fenton, the literary agency Brandt & Brandt, publishers Doubleday, Doran & Company and Farrar & Rinehart, and the Council for Democracy, a propaganda outlet for which Benét wrote radio scripts during Word War II. Such files also exist for fellow alumni of Yale College, including John Franklin Carter and Robert E. McClure, and expats with whom Stephen Vincent and Rosemary Benét socialized while living in Paris in the 1920s. These couples include Philip and Ellen (Semple) Barry, Douglas and Emily Moore, and Richard and Alice Lee Myers. Other correspondents include Hiram Bingham, Norman Cousins, Wilbur L. Cross, John Dos Passos, Arthur Davison Ficke, John Gould Fletcher, Sinclair Lewis, Archibald MacLeish, Kenneth Patchen, Beatrix Potter, Muriel Rukeyser, Carl Sandburg, and Thornton Wilder.
  Stephen Vincent Benét died March 13, 1943, and Rosemary Benét died August 18, 1962. Correspondence marked from 1944 forward in the finding aid, or reflected in a date range that ends 1944 or later, clearly indicates the presence of correspondence to Rosemary Benét. Otherwise, individual letters within mixed files and files consisting exclusively of letters to Rosemary Benét are not indicated.
  The Third Party Correspondence subseries consists of the loose third party correspondence in the series. Most likely these letters came into the Benét's possession as enclosures and, over time, were separated from the original letters.
  - General Correspondence
    - "A" general, 1920-1962, undated (Box 1, Folder 1-2)
    - A. M. Heath Company, 1926 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Abbe, George, 1935-1962, undated (Box 1, Folder 4-7)
    - Academy of American Poets, 1935-1962, undated (Box 1, Folder 8-11)
    - Adams, Franklin P. (Franklin Pierce), 1936-1943, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Corrected proof removed from Adams, Franklin P. (Franklin Pierce), undated (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3103)
    - Adams, G. W., 1934–1935 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Adams, James Truslow, 1941 November (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Adams, Mildred, 1943 April 3 (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - [Addams, Jane?], 1935 October 25 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Adlard, Eleanor, 1934–1935 (Box 1, Folder 17)
    - Albert, Pat, 1930, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Aldrich, Richard, 1937 April 17 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Alfred A. Knopf, Inc., 1933-1951, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
    - Allen, Helen Howe, 1952–1961 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Allen, Hervey, 1928, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 22)
    - Alpha Delta Phi, 1934-1956, undated (Box 1, Folder 23)
    - Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America. Chicago Joint Board, 1941 October 6 (Box 1, Folder 24)
    - America First Committee, 1941 February 18 (Box 1, Folder 25)
    - American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1931-1951, undated (Box 1, Folder 26-27)
    - American Artists Group, 1939 April 14 (Box 1, Folder 28)
    - American Center of P.E.N., 1943 (Box 2, Folder 29)
    - American Council of Learned Societies, 1941 November 3 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - American Eugenics Society, 1937 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - American Foundation for the Blind, 1940 October 24 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - American Friends of Lafayette, 1933 November 13 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - American Institute of Public Opinion, 1936, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 34)
    - American Library Association, 1935 November 29 (Box 2, Folder 35)
    - American Library in Paris, 1940 March 26 (Box 2, Folder 36)
    - American Merchant Marine Library Association, 1936–1937 (Box 2, Folder 37)
    - American Red Cross, 1941 January 6 (Box 2, Folder 38)
    - American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals, 1939 February 6 (Box 2, Folder 39)
    - American Stove Company, 1937 November 18 (Box 2, Folder 40)
    - American Tobacco Company, 1941 September 23 (Box 2, Folder 41)
    - Ames, Lucy, 1940-1959, undated (Box 2, Folder 42)
    - Ames, Winthrop, 1934-1936, undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
    - Amussen, Ted, 1936–1956 (Box 2, Folder 44)
    - Amy Loveman National Award, 1961–1962 (Box 2, Folder 45)
    - Andrews, Charles McLean, 1926-1949, undated (Box 2, Folder 46)
    - Andrews, John W., 1920-1938, undated (Box 2, Folder 47)
    - Angell, James Rowland, 1943 March 16 (Box 2, Folder 48)
    - Arciniegas, German, 1942 June 24 (Box 2, Folder 49)
    - Argus Book Shop, 1940 February 5 (Box 2, Folder 50)
    - Arnold, Harry L. (Harry Loren), 1938 December 23 (Box 2, Folder 51)
    - Atchley, Dana; Atchley, Mory, 1930-1952, undated (Box 2, Folder 52)
    - Atherton, Gertrude Franklin Horn, 1945 January 4 (Box 2, Folder 53)
    - Atkinson, Eleanor, 1932 January 31 (Box 2, Folder 54)
    - Atkinson, Robert W., 1931 November 23 (Box 2, Folder 55)
    - Atlanta Constitution, 1944, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 56)
    - Atlanta University, 1936 Febuary 3 (Box 2, Folder 57)
    - The Atlantic Monthly, 1935-1950, undated (Box 2, Folder 58)
    - Atlantic Monthly Press, 1923–1946 (Box 2, Folder 59)
    - Arts Decoration, 1934 July 7 (Box 2, Folder 60)
    - Auchincloss, Adele, undated (Box 2, Folder 61)
    - Authors' Guild (U.S.), 1914 October 15 (Box 2, Folder 62)
    - Authors' League of America, 1933–1945 (Box 2, Folder 63)
    - Axelson, Mary McDougal, 1932–1935 (Box 2, Folder 64)
    - Ayres, Elizabeth, 1926 March 7 (Box 2, Folder 65)
    - "B" general, 1919-1962, undated (Box 2, Folder 66-70)
    - Bachelor, Joseph M. (Joseph Morris), 1941 November 8 (Box 2, Folder 71)
    - Bacon, Leonard, 1928-1951, undated (Box 2, Folder 72)
    - Bacon, Peggy, 1942 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 73)
    - Badger, Shreve Cowles, 1920-1946, undated (Box 2, Folder 74)
    - Baer, Arthur, 1938, undated (Box 3, Folder 75)
    - Bair, Frederick H[aigh?], 1937 (Box 3, Folder 76)
    - Bakeless, John, 1938, undated (Box 3, Folder 77)
    - Balaÿ, [?ette], 1924, undated (Box 3, Folder 78)
    - Baldwin, Faith, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 79)
    - Baldwin, Sherman, 1928–1946 (Box 3, Folder 80)
    - Baliev, N. F. (Nikita Fedorovich), 1921 February (Box 3, Folder 81)
    - Barclay, Dorothy, 1937 August 21 (Box 3, Folder 82)
    - Barker, Shirley, 1933 July 8 (Box 3, Folder 83)
    - Barlow, Samuel L. M. (Samuel Latham Mitchell), 1946-1959, undated (Box 3, Folder 84)
    - Barnet B. Ruder (Firm), 1936 January 27 (Box 3, Folder 85)
    - Barnitz, Richard, 1938-1942, undated (Box 3, Folder 86)
    - Barry, Philip; Barry, Ellen, 1924-1961, undated (Box 3, Folder 87-90)
    - Clippings removed from Barry, Philip, 1949 December 4 (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3104)
    - Bartsch, Hans, 1939 March 15 (Box 3, Folder 91)
    - Basford, Emory Shelvy, 1937 August 18 (Box 3, Folder 92)
    - Bassett, Richard, 1920 July (Box 3, Folder 93)
    - Basshe, Em Jo, 1938 September 27 (Box 3, Folder 94)
    - [Bates?], Ralph, undated (Box 3, Folder 95)
    - Bates College (Lewiston, Me.), 1936 December 11 (Box 3, Folder 96)
    - Batten, Barton, Durstine Osborn, Inc., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 97)
    - Beale, Howard K. (Howard Kennedy), 1943 March 14 (Box 3, Folder 98)
    - Beals, Walter B., 1929, undated (Box 3, Folder 99)
    - Bechtel, Louise Seaman, undated (Box 3, Folder 100)
    - Beebe, William, undated (Box 3, Folder 101)
    - Belitt, Ben, 1934 (Box 3, Folder 102)
    - Bellinger, Alfred R. (Alfred Raymond), 1940, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 103)
    - Belmont, Eleanor [Robson?], 1934–1941 (Box 3, Folder 104)
    - Belth, Norton, 1941 September 9 (Box 3, Folder 105)
    - Bennett, Emmett L. (Emmett Leslie), 1937 May 20 (Box 3, Folder 106)
    - Bennett, Russell H., 1942 (Box 3, Folder 107)
    - Berry, Romeyn, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 108)
    - Beston, Henry, 1937 January 8 (Box 3, Folder 109)
    - Betti, Adolfo, 1938 June 30 (Box 3, Folder 110)
    - Bianchi, Martha Dickinson, undated (Box 3, Folder 111)
    - Biddle, Constance, 1933–1934 (Box 3, Folder 112)
    - Bingham, Hiram, 1939 November 9 (Box 3, Folder 113)
    - Bingham, Seth, 1932–1943 (Box 3, Folder 114)
    - Biossat, Bruce, undated (Box 3, Folder 115)
    - Bishop, John Peale, 1928-1944, undated (Box 3, Folder 116)
    - [Bishop?], Margaret, 1938-1953, undated (Box 3, Folder 117)
    - Bizot, Maguy, 1923-1952, undated (Box 3, Folder 118)
    - Black, Robert C., 1937 November 2 (Box 3, Folder 119)
    - Blake, Dorothy, undated (Box 3, Folder 120)
    - Blakeslee, Victor F. (Victor Franklin), 1942 August 10 (Box 3, Folder 121)
    - Blankfort, Michael, undated (Box 3, Folder 122)
    - Blankner, Frederika, undated (Box 3, Folder 123)
    - Bloomingdale's (Firm), [1941] (Box 3, Folder 124)
    - Blue Network Company, 1943 February 17 (Box 3, Folder 125)
    - Blunt, Hugh Francis, 1928 November 18 (Box 3, Folder 126)
    - B'nai B'rith. Anti-defamation League, 1961–1962 (Box 3, Folder 127)
    - Clipping from from B'nai B'rith. Anti-defamation League, 1962 January 4 (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3105)
    - Boase, T. S. R. (Thomas Sherrer Ross), 1934 August 4 (Box 3, Folder 128)
    - Bobbs-Merrill Company, 1938–1939 (Box 3, Folder 129)
    - Bohn, Wm. E. (William Edward), 1930-1940, undated (Box 4, Folder 130)
    - Book-of-the-Month Club, 1937-1962, undated (Box 4, Folder 131-133)
    - The Bookman, 1919 October 20 (Box 4, Folder 134)
    - Boots, Ralph Henderson, 1936–1943 (Box 4, Folder 135)
    - Boyce, Burk, 1942 February 14 (Box 4, Folder 136)
    - Boyd, James; Boyd, Katharine, 1940-1941, undated (Box 4, Folder 137)
    - Boylston, Helen Dore, 1933 December 4 (Box 4, Folder 138)
    - Boynton, Percy Holmes, undated (Box 4, Folder 139)
    - Bracker, Jon, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 140)
    - Bradford, Gamaliel, 1931 October (Box 4, Folder 141)
    - Brady, William A., 1924 October 3 (Box 4, Folder 142)
    - Braithwaite, William Stanley, 1958 September 30 (Box 4, Folder 143)
    - Braley, Berton, 1936 January 22 (Box 4, Folder 144)
    - Brandt & Brandt, 1921-1962, undated (Box 4, Folder 145-152)
    - Branford College (Yale University), undated (Box 4, Folder 153)
    - Branscombe, Gena, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 154)
    - Brearley School, 1935-1943, undated (Box 4, Folder 155)
    - Brewer, Joseph, 1931–1943 (Box 4, Folder 156)
    - Brick Row Book Shop (New York, N.Y.), 1928-1941, undated (Box 4, Folder 157)
    - British Information Services, 1942 June 6 (Box 4, Folder 158)
    - British War Relief Society (U.S.), 1941 January 31 (Box 4, Folder 159)
    - Brittain, Vera, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 160)
    - Bromfield, Louis, 1938 October 18 (Box 4, Folder 161)
    - Bromley, Dorothy Dunbar, 1924-1943, undated (Box 4, Folder 162)
    - Brooks, Van Wyck, 1938-1943, undated (Box 4, Folder 163)
    - Brooks School (North Andover, Mass.), 1940 (Box 5, Folder 164)
    - Brown, H. Tatnall, Jr., 1940 September 15 (Box 5, Folder 165)
    - Brown, John Mason; Brown, Cassie, 1946-1961, undated (Box 5, Folder 166-167)
    - Brown, William Adams, 1929 January 23 (Box 5, Folder 168)
    - Brown Brothers, Harriman & Co., 1953, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 169)
    - Brown University. Library, 1947 January 18 (Box 5, Folder 170)
    - Bruce, Robert V., 1953 (Box 5, Folder 171)
    - Brush, Katherine, 1940, undated (Box 5, Folder 172)
    - Bryn Mawr College, 1946, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 173)
    - Buck, Pearl S. (Pearl Sydenstricker), 1934 November 26 (Box 5, Folder 174)
    - The Buckley School, 1939, 1941 (Box 5, Folder 175)
    - Bucky, Frida Sarsen, 1940 September 13 (Box 5, Folder 176)
    - Buechner, Frederick, undated (Box 5, Folder 177)
    - [Bullard, Helen?], 1936 September 2 (Box 5, Folder 178)
    - Bundy, McGeorge, 1940 August 6 (Box 5, Folder 179)
    - Bunting, Charles H., undated (Box 5, Folder 180)
    - Burke, Shirley, 1942 March 10 (Box 5, Folder 181)
    - Burlingham, Charles C. [(Charles Culp)?], 1942 February 8 (Box 5, Folder 182)
    - Burnett, Whit, 1944-1961, undated (Box 5, Folder 183)
    - Burt, Maxwell Struthers, 1942 September 21 (Box 5, Folder 184)
    - Butcher, Fanny, 1923 January 5 (Box 5, Folder 185)
    - Byard, Ella N., 1943, undated (Box 5, Folder 186)
    - Bynner, Witter, 1923 February 19 (Box 5, Folder 187)
    - "C" general, 1921-1957, undated (Box 5, Folder 188-191)
    - Cabell, James Branch, 1939-1943, undated (Box 5, Folder 192)
    - [Cahill?], Holger, 1935 February 25 (Box 5, Folder 193)
    - Calhoun College (Yale University), 1933–1940 (Box 5, Folder 194)
    - California Shipbuilding Corporation, 1943 (Box 5, Folder 195)
    - Call, Mary M[arshall?], 1943 March 15 (Box 5, Folder 196)
    - Cameron, M[ary?] E[mily?], 1939 June 21 (Box 5, Folder 197)
    - Campbell, Donald M., 1926-1943, undated (Box 5, Folder 198)
    - Campbell, Kane, 1937 October 11 (Box 5, Folder 199)
    - Campbell, Wallace, undated (Box 5, Folder 200)
    - Canby, Henry Seidel, 1937-1953, undated (Box 5, Folder 201)
    - Canfield, Cass, 1941–1952 (Box 5, Folder 202)
    - Cannon, Le Grand, Jr., 1937 June 3 (Box 5, Folder 203)
    - Cardozo, Benjamin N. (Benjamin Nathan), 1933 November 01 (Box 5, Folder 204)
    - Carl Fischer, Inc., 1940 March 13 (Box 5, Folder 205)
    - Carmer, Carl, 1950 June 6 (Box 5, Folder 206)
    - Carnegie Library of Pittsburgh, 1941 August 8 (Box 5, Folder 207)
    - Carpenter, C. C. J., 1938 November 28 (Box 5, Folder 208)
    - Carpenter, Margaret, 1958–1959 (Box 5, Folder 209)
    - Carroll, Gladys Hasty, 1943 March 16 (Box 5, Folder 210)
    - Carter, Henry, 1921-1960, undated (Box 5, Folder 211)
    - Carter, John Franklin, 1919-1960, undated (Box 6, Folder 212-216)
    - Cate, Wirt Armistead, 1938 April 29 (Box 6, Folder 217)
    - Cather, Willa, 1943 March 31 (Box 6, Folder 218)
    - Cavalcade of America (copies), 1942 (Box 6, Folder 219)
    - Century Association (New York, N.Y.), 1933–1943 (Box 6, Folder 220)
    - Century Club (New York, N.Y.), 1940 March 1 (Box 6, Folder 221)
    - Chandler, "Bebo", 1959, undated (Box 6, Folder 222)
    - Chapin, Katherine Garrison, [?] March 4 (Box 6, Folder 223)
    - Charles Scribner's Sons, 1920–1940 (Box 6, Folder 224)
    - Chase, Enoch A. (Enoch Aquila), 1941 March 25 (Box 6, Folder 225)
    - Chase, Harry Woodburn, 1939 December 8 (Box 6, Folder 226)
    - Chase, Stuart, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 227)
    - Chi Delta Theta (Yale University), 1916 November 7 (Box 6, Folder 228)
    - Child, Charles, 1933-1943, undated (Box 6, Folder 229)
    - Letters removed from Child, Charles, undated (Box 123 (Oversize), Folder 3106)
    - Child Study Association of America, 1932–1940 (Box 6, Folder 230)
    - Children's Crusade for Children, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 231)
    - Chisholm, Hugh, 1935–1936 (Box 6, Folder 232)
    - Choate, Ann Hyde, 1943 April 02 (Box 6, Folder 233)
    - Chubb, Thomas Caldecot, 1935–1941 (Box 6, Folder 234)
    - Church, Ted, 1938, undated (Box 6, Folder 235)
    - Church Peace Union, 1942 June 9 (Box 6, Folder 236)
    - Chute, B. J. (Beatrice Joy), 1957 August 2 (Box 6, Folder 237)
    - Citizens for Victory, 1943–1944 (Box 6, Folder 238)
    - Claar, Roy H., 1940–1941 (Box 6, Folder 239)
    - Clark, Dorothy Park, 1940 March 13 (Box 6, Folder 240)
    - Clark H. Getts, Inc., 1937, 1943 (Box 6, Folder 241)
    - Clemens, Cyril, 1927-1949, undated (Box 6, Folder 242)
    - Cleveland Museum of Art, undated (Box 6, Folder 243)
    - Clift, Glenn, 1935–1936 (Box 6, Folder 244)
    - Coale, Griffith Baily; Coale, Elizabeth, 1942-1954, undated (Box 6, Folder 245)
    - Coblenz, Stanton A. (Stanton Arthur), 1930, 1936 (Box 6, Folder 246)
    - Coffee House (Club: New York, N.Y.), 1942 October 19 (Box 6, Folder 247)
    - Coffin, Isabelle Pine, 1931 October 17 (Box 6, Folder 248)
    - Cohn, Louis Henry, 1939-1943, undated (Box 6, Folder 249)
    - Colby College, 1937 April 20 (Box 6, Folder 250)
    - Cole, Evelyn; Cole Walter, 1941-1947, undated (Box 6, Folder 251)
    - College Humor, 1926, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 252)
    - College Poetry Society of America, 1939 (Box 6, Folder 253)
    - Collura, Ida M., 1961-1962, undated (Box 6, Folder 254)
    - Colony, Horatio, 1935–1943 (Box 6, Folder 255)
    - The Colophon, 1933, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 256)
    - Colum, Mary, 1942 October 4 (Box 6, Folder 257)
    - Colum, Padraic, 1941 January 24 (Box 6, Folder 258)
    - Columbia Broadcasting System, Inc., 1941-1943, undated (Box 6, Folder 259)
    - Columbia University, 1929–1944 (Box 6, Folder 260)
    - Commager, Henry Steele, 1960 January 5 (Box 6, Folder 261)
    - Committee for National Morale, 1941–1942 (Box 6, Folder 262)
    - Committee to Defend America by Aiding the Allies, 1940 June 26 (Box 6, Folder 263)
    - Condé Nast Press, undated (Box 6, Folder 264)
    - Connelly, Marc, 1939, undated (Box 7, Folder 265)
    - Considine, John W., Jr., 1930 June 20 (Box 7, Folder 266)
    - Cooper, Louise, 1953–1962 (Box 7, Folder 267)
    - Cooper Union for the Advancement of Science and Art, 1943 December 14 (Box 7, Folder 268)
    - Cope, [Eliza?] M., 1932-1933, undated (Box 7, Folder 269)
    - Corwin, Emil, 1943 (Box 7, Folder 270)
    - Corwin, Norman, 1942 February 4 (Box 7, Folder 271)
    - The Cosmopolitan Club, 1933-1959, undated (Box 7, Folder 272-273)
    - Council for Democracy, 1940-1944, undated (Box 7, Folder 274-276)
    - The Country Gentleman, 1937 February 4 (Box 7, Folder 277-278)
    - The Countryman Press, Inc., 1936-1938, undated (Box 7, Folder 279)
    - Courlander, Harold, 1940-1941, undated (Box 7, Folder 280)
    - Cousins, Norman, 1941, 1955 (Box 7, Folder 281)
    - Coward, Edward Fales, Mrs., 1938 (Box 7, Folder 282)
    - Coward, Thomas R.; Coward, Marian, 1919-1944, undated (Box 7, Folder 283)
    - Coyle, Kathleen, 1940-1943, undated (Box 7, Folder 284)
    - Cozzens, James Gould; Cozzens, Mrs., 1958 March 7 (Box 7, Folder 285)
    - Cragin, Georgina Marshall, 1934-1938, undated (Box 7, Folder 286)
    - Crampton, Henry Edward, 1941 October 23 (Box 7, Folder 287)
    - Crane, Josephine Boardman, 1934 March 15 (Box 7, Folder 288)
    - [Cravin?], Margaret, 1939 October 12 (Box 7, Folder 289)
    - Crockett, Lucy Herndon, undated (Box 7, Folder 290)
    - Cross, Wilbur L. (Wilbur Lucius), 1919–1937 (Box 7, Folder 291)
    - Cruikshank, R. J. (Robert James), 1941-1942, undated (Box 7, Folder 292)
    - Culver, Henry B. (Henry Brundage), 1943 March 15 (Box 7, Folder 293)
    - Culver Military Academy, 1938 July 8 (Box 7, Folder 294)
    - Cumming, Mary [Gairdner Smith?], 1942–1943 (Box 7, Folder 295)
    - Curtis, "Charlie"; Curtis, "Freddie", 1929-1958, undated (Box 7, Folder 296)
    - "D" general, 1903-1958, undated (Box 7, Folder 297-299)
    - D. Appleton-Century Company, 1943 August 25 (Box 7, Folder 300)
    - D. C. Heath and Company, 1931, 1944 (Box 7, Folder 301)
    - D. W. Griffiths Productions, undated (Box 7, Folder 302)
    - DaCosta, Jean, 1929–1943 (Box 7, Folder 303)
    - Dalphin, Marcia, 1934, undated (Box 7, Folder 304)